Chihabeddine Merabet

Graphic designer



Personal details



Chihabeddine Merabet



chihab0507@gmail.com



+213666324206



Nº: 01, Cité 40 Logts LSP Lababsa, BT: 01, El-Eulma, Sétif El Eulma, Sétif, Algeria



July 5, 2002





chihab-merabet.github.io



linkedin.com/chihab-merabet

Skills

Adobe Photoshop	••••
Adobe Illustrator	••••
Video editing	••••
Langage C	••••
Java	••••
HTML, CSS	••••
Languages	

Languages

Arabic	••••
French	••••
English	••••

Education

High school

Sep 2017 - Sep 2020

El chiheb high school, El Eulma

Graduated and earned Baccalaureate with a degree of 16.06/20.

University

Dec 2020 - Present

École Nationale Supérieure de Télécommunications et de Technologies de l'information et des communications (ENSTTIC), Oran Forth year student.

Employment

Communications responsible

2021 - 2022

Horizon Club, Oran

Vice-president

2022 - Present

Horizon Club, Oran

Profile

My name is Chihabeddine Merabet and I am 20 years old, I live in Sétif, I study in ENSTTIC, a school of engineering in Oran, I am passionate about graphic design, programming and web development, I have skills in various tools and languages.

Internships

Intern

Jun 2022 - Jul 2022

Algérie Télécom, El Eulma

Earned skills in FTTH, Amplification Centre, Networking.